Hello friends, the virus is spreading rapidly in the country and the world.
To deal with this, health insurance has
become an essential weapon. It
provides financial security in adverse circumstances.
If you have not yet taken insurance cover,
then you can take such a plan which can bear the
entire cost of treatment in case of infection from Corona.
Friends, keeping in mind the Corona, many companies have
launched many such plans in which you get a
good cover in very less money,
which
can provide you financial help in the treatment of Corona. So friends, in this video,
I will tell you about two such plans,
one is of ICICI Lombard and the
other is Bajaj Allianz General Insurance. So
friends, what is Plan Pehelwan? If you
know about ICSE, then it has come up with an
insurance policy to deal with the Corona virus. Friends,
this is a group insurance policy type. So,
under this policy, the insurance company will
pay the entire amount immediately if the virus test comes positive at any government office. The insurance amount is given only when the
disease is detected during the policy period.
Suppose a person has taken
this policy.  If you have taken the vaccine and he
turns out to be Corona positive here, he will be
given Rs. 25000 immediately,
but friends, here the policy has to be taken for 14
days,
like all you have taken, it is for 14 days, you
cannot do it next,
after 14 days you can click on it
and the policy tender will be for one year, that is,
you have to pay Rs. 159 for one
year and there you will
get Rs. 25 thousand, if you
turn out to be Corona positive, then the
insurance amount in the UK introduction cover of the ward will be Rs.
25000, as I told you,
its
medium is Rs. 150, that is, you will spend Rs. 160,
in this policy you are also offered health
assistant and virtual assistant, ambulance
assistant and technical sentence through chat
and this policy benefit can be taken only by the person of 18 to 75
years of age, so
friends, what is the second policy here, that is, for Rs. 199  This is
Bajaj Allianz General Insurance, and
its name is Karona Care. The Kuru Crop
Insurance Policy costs ₹199 (
approximately ₹200). Suppose you have one year insurance cover,
and virus-infected
people will get insurance cover of up to ₹50,000.
This insurance cover can be availed by
individuals below the age of 18. The
daughter of a farmer cannot avail this policy.
It is also reported that this will be
valid in any hospital that treats the virus, meaning
you can get treatment of ₹50,000 in whichever hospital you get treatment from. Not only this,
you
can also include the expenses incurred in hospitalization and post-care medical treatment within one month. If you are
hospitalized today, you can claim for the month before
and one month after this.
You can buy the Kuru Care policy from home through your mobile phone.
As I have told you here, you
can also see on the screen how you can get
this on the phone. You can also claim these two
policies.  You can buy it, for this you do
not need to do any medical test at all. Secondly, friends,
if you have Ayushman Bharat PM Jan
Aagya card, then through that also you can get
free treatment here, you can get the
test done in the lab and hospital, this is also our scheme,
under this the
beneficiaries of this scheme can get their treatment,
its testing can be done by subscribing and if you
subscribe for free in advance, then you can
take full advantage of it here.
Apart from this, friends, if you want to get
extra protection, then you
can take these insurance policies, which are very
less, in 150 you are getting a cover of 25 thousand rupees
and in this you are getting a cover of 50 thousand rupees
here. Friends, how did you like it, like it,
share it and subscribe to the channel
so that you can get similar videos.